themeowpost.com 2017-12-01

# Privacy Policy | The Meow Post

This privacy policy will set out how TheMeowPost.com uses and protects any information that you give when you use TheMeowPost.com.

TheMeowPost.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is completely protected and work hard to make sure all precautions are taken.  We cannot guaranty anything, but do everything within our means to ensure your privacy outlined within these terms. If we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can rest assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

TheMeowPost.com may change this policy at any time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes that may occur. This policy is effective from Nov 1, 2014.

We may ask to collect the following information:

  * Your e-mail address (for use to send you the daily or weekly TheMeowPost newsletter, which you can unsubscribe from at any time as you wish by contacting us)
  * Pictures, videos, and stories (If you send us any pictures, videos, or stories, you agree to give us full indisputable rights to share and distribute any content you may send us.  By submitting any content to TheMeowPost.com, you agree that the content does not violate or infringe on anyones rights or otherwise violates the law in any way. You also grant us a perpetual, irrevocable, royalty-free, non-exclusive, unrestricted, worldwide license to publicly display your content on TheMeowPost.com and any of our social network channels.  If you do not specify otherwise, your name may be used within the re-distrabuton of any content you send us.  You may kindly specify how you want your name to be used by emailing

We are dedicated to ensuring that all your information is secure and used as stated.  In our best attempt to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to aid in safeguarding any secure information we collect online.  If in the unlikely event that any personal information is leaked, or a breach occurs, we will not be responsible for any negative repercussions.

## **How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in **no way** gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but in most cases you can modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of our website and its features, but the choice is yours.

## **Third Party Vendors**

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a your prior web site visits.
  * Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads via Google AdSense to you based on your visits to TheMeowPost and/or other sites on the Internet.

## **Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we **do not** have any control that other website in any way. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question that you visit when exiting our website.

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, content removal, or advertising, please contact us at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#7a0e121f171f150d0a15090e3a1d171b131654191517)
